

PROFILE

8+ Years' of experience as educationist strong knowledge about training and development methods, exam management, accreditation process, course contents development and LMS tools handling, design thinking. More than 20 workshops conducted for students and staffs and more than 30 workshops attended in career. Worked as examiner, supervisor, controller, moderator, online exam coordinator and paper setter for university and MSBTE.

Believe in hands on practical projectbased learning approach to deliver creative skills.

CONTACT

Mobile No. +91- 9096679875

EMAIL:

satish.pise.sgp@gmail.com

Web Profile

https://www.linkedin.com/in/satish-pise/satish20p.github.io/index.html

HOBBIES

Spirituality,

Travelling,

Movies and Acts.

SATISH PISE

Technical Trainer

EDUCATION

Government College of Engineering, Jalgaon

2008 - 2011

Bachelor of Engineering - Computer Engineering.

RKDF Institute of Science & Technology, Bhopal

2015 - 2018

Master of Technology - Computer Science & Engineering.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Current Employment - Edunet Foundation - Master Trainer

2nd Jan 2020 – Till Date

Conduct training related to cloud computing and application development, Work with project manager to manage and conduct trainings for staff and students, design course material and documents, design training program.

Past 1 - Sanjay Ghodawat Polytechnic, Atigre - Lecturer

1st June 2013 to 7th July 2015 (25 Months) & 1st July 2016 to 31st Dec 2019 Mentoring, motivating students as a lecturer, working as a lab in-charge, course files and course material development, Spoken Tutorial Project IIT Bombay Coordinator. Organizing and conducting trainings for student and staff, In-plant-training coordinator.

Past 2 - Samarth Polytechnic, Belhe - Lecturer

5th August 2012 – 6th April 2013

Teaching - Subject Taught – Computer Fundamental, Management Information System.

Past 3 - Late. N. B. Chhabada Institute of Engineering, Satara - Lecturer $1^{\rm st}$ August $2011-30^{\rm th}$ July 2012

Teaching, guiding and motivating students and work as a lab in-charge & TPO Coordinator. Subject Taught – Web Technology, Network Engineering

SKILLS

Cloud Computing Oracle SQL/PLSQL

NodeJS Java Programming

MongoDB Computer Networking

Cybersecurity Web Development

Design Thinking IBM Cloud